# Tauras Semaška

Kamanų 4, Kaunas, 46466

Mob: +37066403515 Email: tstauras100@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

A proactive, confident and self-motivated individual with warehouse experience. I have spent 12 years living in the United Kingdom and want to return to Lithuania to live and work. Trustworthy, punctual and committed to delivering excellent service. A strong team player who enjoys the challenge of new tasks and works confidently under pressure using own initiative to solve problems effectively. A passion for Engineering and IT, excellent Skills and the ability to plan and prioritise workload. Learns new tasks and skills quickly.

#### **KEY SKILLS / ATTRIBUTES**

- Excellent communication and time management skills
- Strong and effective organisational and interpersonal skills with a proactive flexible approach to manage changing priorities
- Enjoys meeting challenges and seeing them through, maintaining high standards throughout
- Demonstrates meticulous attention to detail and high levels of concentration and focus
- Displays a strong personal commitment to successfully completing all projects

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

# **ECHO PERSONNEL (Northampton)**

Aug 2017 - Nov 2017

#### Picker Packer

- Worked as part of a close-knit team, picking and packing products to a high standard and to tight timescales
- Responsible for ensuring all the products were correctly labelled and scanned
- Maintained the warehouse to high standards, ensuring the floors, shelves and machinery were kept clean and free from any hazards, minimising any accidents
- Demonstrated the ability to perform repetitive tasks quickly and accurately without compromising quality
- Exhibited a high level of concentration skills with a keen eye for detail
- Displayed a responsible attitude towards safe working practices coupled with a safety conscious approach to work
- Worked individually as well as part of a team, demonstrating flexibility and motivation
- Developed good communication, interpersonal and time management skills
- Occasionally required to work on own initiative and solve problems without any direct supervision
- Developed a disciplined and organised approach to prioritise the workload in a production environment
- Enjoyed working in a fast paced, pressurised environment and meeting tight deadlines
- Complied with strict Health and Safety, Fire Awareness and Security procedures, policies and standards

#### **EVENTS PEOPLE (Northampton)**

Jun 2017 - Oct 2017

# Car Park/Security Attendant

- Protected vehicles left in the car park through continuous monitoring and patrolling, preventing any theft or damage
- Worked as part of a team ensuring full security measures were implemented and the car park was safe and secure during the day.
- Effectively communicated with people at all levels and from different backgrounds
- Able to use own initiative and make quick and effective decisions when dealing with unexpected situations
- Demonstrated the ability to work independently without any supervision and maintain attention to detail and composure
- Great time management skills with the ability to work unsociable hours

- Displayed the confidence to challenge people as and when necessary
- Capable of working a varied hours, working outdoors and in all weather conditions
- Complied with strict Health and Safety, Fire Awareness, Security and Welfare procedures, policies and standards

### **BEACHMARKETING (Northampton)**

Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

- updating wordpress websites. updating plugins. fixing errors. and doing custom coding.
- managing basic domain names, ip's and DNS
- supervising site security. and updating what's needed.
- basic pen testing (kali linux) to find, try and exploit websites.
- some customer tech support / working with clients tech teams on projects
- internal support, helping colleagues with coding / technical issues
- hardware support, updating / advising on some out of date hardware in the company and a few other things

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

- Software Development Level 2 merit grade. Engineering Level 2 double grade merit pass, Northampton College, Northampton
- GCSE's in Maths, English Literature, Science, PE, Food Technology and Computer Science, Malcolm Arnold School, Northampton
- Learning web development coding with the help of code institute online courses.
- BCS Level 3 Certificate in Programming.
- BCS Level 3 Certificate in Software Development Context and Methodologies
- · Level 3 in Engineering.

#### **IT SKILLS**

• Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Data base, Internet, Email,

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION / INTERESTS**

• Deep Sea fishing, DIY especially woodwork. Fault finding and repairs on computers. Speaks 2 languages fluently, Lithuanian and English.

References available upon request

Petronela Barz.

Email: <u>petron3lla@yahoo.com</u> Phone number: +44 7429203366

Northampton College Booth Lane.

Email: enquiries@northamptoncollege.ac.uk

Phone number: +44 1604 734567

Steve Bishop

Email: <u>steve@beachmarketing.co.uk</u> phone number: +44 7833100979